{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"747/83",
			"answer":"747/83",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"388/97",
			"answer":"388/97",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"858/78",
			"answer":"858/78",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"260/10",
			"answer":"260/10",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"192/16",
			"answer":"192/16",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"630/63",
			"answer":"630/63",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"352/32",
			"answer":"352/32",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"360/15",
			"answer":"360/15",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"420/60",
			"answer":"420/60",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"136/68",
			"answer":"136/68",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7.84/0.49",
			"answer":"7.84/0.49",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"35.6/8.9",
			"answer":"35.6/8.9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.243/0.81",
			"answer":"0.243/0.81",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"17.6/8.8",
			"answer":"17.6/8.8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2.25/0.45",
			"answer":"2.25/0.45",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"57.6/4.8",
			"answer":"57.6/4.8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7.38/0.18",
			"answer":"7.38/0.18",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.039/3.9",
			"answer":"0.039/3.9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"86.4/4.8",
			"answer":"86.4/4.8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.525/0.35",
			"answer":"0.525/0.35",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}